{
    "questions": [
      {
        "id":"Q1",
        "question":"Who is the lead actor in the Baahubali series?",
        "answer":"PRABHAS",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q2",
        "question":"Which Bollywood actor is involved in a blackbuck hunting case controversy?",
        "answer":"SALMAN",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q3",
        "question":"What is the highest-grossing Indian film of all time ?",
        "answer":"BAHUBALI",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q4",
        "question":"Who played the lead role of Padmavati in the movie Padmaavat?",
        "answer":"DEEPIKA",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q5",
        "question":"Which film is known for the iconic dialogue Mere paas maa hai?",
        "answer":"DEEWAR",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q6",
        "question":"What is the title of the first Indian 3D dance film?",
        "answer":"ABCD",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q7",
        "question":"What is the name of India's highest-grossing film of all time?",
        "answer":"DANGAL",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q8",
        "question":"In 2019, which film starred Vicky Kaushal as an army officer?",
        "answer":"URI",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q9",
        "question":"Which Bollywood actor is known as the Bhai of the industry?",
        "answer":"SALMAN",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      },
      {
        "id":"Q10",
        "question":"Who holds the title Khiladi in the world of Bollywood today?",
        "answer":"AKSHAY",
        "answer1":["PRABHAS", "BAHUBALI", "DEEPIKA", "DEEWAR", "ABCD", "DANGAL", "URI", "SALMAN", "AKSHAY"]
      }
    ]
    

  }